[
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who established Lodi Dyansty",
        "answer": "Bahlul Khan Lodi",
        "choices": [
            "Bahlul Khan Lodi",
            "Sikandr Khan Lodi",
            "Malik Sultan Khan Lodi",
            "Ibrahim Lodi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "First Sikh Guru",
        "answer": "Guru Nanak",
        "choices": [
            "Guru Nanak",
            "Guru Angad",
            "Guru Gobind Singh",
            "Guru Hargobind"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Which year marks fall of Constantinople",
        "answer": 1453,
        "choices": [
            1453,
            1454,
            1452,
            1455
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who discovered America",
        "answer": "Christopher Columbus",
        "choices": [
            "Christopher Columbus",
            "Vasco Da Gama",
            "Prince Henry The Navigator",
            "Captain Hawkins"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Treaty of Tordesillias was signed between",
        "answer": "Spain & Portugal",
        "choices": [
            "Spain & Portugal",
            "Spain & England",
            "Portugal & England",
            "Greece & Spain"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Last ruling dynasty of Delhi Sultanate",
        "answer": "Lodi",
        "choices": [
            "Lodi",
            "Mameluk",
            "Tughlaq",
            "Khalji"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "First ruling dynasty of Delhi Sultanate",
        "answer": "Mameluk",
        "choices": [
            "Mameluk",
            "Lodi",
            "Tughlaq",
            "Khalji"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Name the ruler who led to the fall of Constantinople",
        "answer": "Mehmed II",
        "choices": [
            "Mehmed II",
            "Ibrahim II",
            "Murad II",
            "Bayezid II"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who established the Agra city",
        "answer": "Sikhander Khan Lodi",
        "choices": [
            "Sikhander Khan Lodi",
            "Malik Sultan Khan Lodi",
            "Ibrahim Lodi",
            "Ibrahim Lodi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who discovered all sea route from Europe to India",
        "answer": "Vasco Da Gama",
        "choices": [
            "Vasco Da Gama",
            "Christopher Columbus",
            "Captain Hawkins",
            "Afonso de Albuquerque"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who established the Mughal Empire",
        "answer": "Babur",
        "choices": [
            "Babur",
            "Akbar",
            "Jahangir",
            "Shah Jahan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who restored the Grand Trunk Road from the river Indus in the west to Sonargaon in Bengal",
        "answer": "Sher Shah Suri",
        "choices": [
            "Sher Shah Suri",
            "Humayun",
            "Shah Jahan",
            "Akbar"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Thomas Roe, the royal envoy of the king of England visited court of which ruler in India",
        "answer": "Jahangir",
        "choices": [
            "Jahangir",
            "Akbar",
            "Humayun",
            "Aurangzeb"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who constructed the Taj Mahal",
        "answer": "Shah Jahan",
        "choices": [
            "Shah Jahan",
            "Akbar",
            "Humayun",
            "Aurangzeb"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who executed Guru Tegh Bahadur",
        "answer": "Aurangzeb",
        "choices": [
            "Aurangzeb",
            "Akbar",
            "Humayun",
            "Shah Jahan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Sikh Guru born in Bihar",
        "answer": "Guru Gobind Singh",
        "choices": [
            "Guru Gobind Singh",
            "Guru Tegh Bahadu",
            "Guru Nanak",
            "Guru Angad"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who established the Maratha Kingdom",
        "answer": "Shivaji",
        "choices": [
            "Shivaji",
            "Shambhaji",
            "Nana Pahadi",
            "Tanhaji"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "The Khalsa, warrior group of Sikh was established by",
        "answer": "Guru Gobind Singh",
        "choices": [
            "Guru Gobind Singh",
            "Guru Nanak",
            "Guru Tegh Bahadur",
            "Guru Angad"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "In which year was the first regulating act passed to regulate the administration of the East India Company in India",
        "answer": 1773,
        "choices": [
            1773,
            1774,
            1775,
            1772
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "In which year Pitt's India Act enacted",
        "answer": 1784,
        "choices": [
            1784,
            1783,
            1786,
            1785
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who introduced Permanent Settlement system of revenue collection",
        "answer": "Charles Cornwallis",
        "choices": [
            "Charles Cornwallis",
            "Warren Hastings",
            "Robert Clive",
            "William Pitt"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who introduced the system of Subsidiary Alliance",
        "answer": "Richard Wellesley",
        "choices": [
            "Richard Wellesley",
            "Charles Cornwallis",
            "Warren Hastings",
            "Robert Clive"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "History1450Onwards",
        "question": "Who established the Sikh Empire",
        "answer": "Ranjit Singh",
        "choices": [
            "Ranjit Singh",
            "Guru Gobind",
            "Guru Nanak",
            "Prithviraj Chouhan"
        ]
    }
]